Noah J. Holt

Email: noahjmholt@gmail.com

Cell: 803.468.3236

Security Clearance: Able to Obtain

EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Pursuing a full-time career in Computer Science. Wanting to explore the field of computer science and reach my niche. Interests I have found in the field include app development, security, networks, and data science. Though I have explored these fields, I feel I have barely scratched their surfaces leaving curiosity and interests to explore.

Goal and results oriented communicator, training, and ability to work well in highly stressful situations and environments. One year of education based IT troubleshooting and assistance, with an extra 2+ years of customer service and relationship building experience.

EDUCATION

University of Colorado-Colorado Springs: Bachelor's in Computer Science, May 2024 PIMA Medical Institute: Associates of Veterinary Technology, May 2020

CERTIFICATIONS

CompTIA A+, Cert #: COMP001022097585

SUMMARY OF SKILLS, TOOLS, AND TECHNOLOGIES:

Java, C, C#, C++, R, Python	Object Oriented Programming	Microsoft Office Suites
Docker and AWS	Bash Scripting	Training and Education
Git and GitHub	Window, MacOS and Linux Operating Systems	Rugby Coach
WordPress, Django, TypeScript	IT Service Desk Tier 1 and 2	CPR and BLS Certified
Restful API	Agile Frameworks	

PROJECT WORK EXPERIENCE

Secret Santa Wish List, Class Project: Sep 2023 – Dec 2023

Created wish list Web app for users to login, add items viewable to the public.

- Implemented CRUD application with one-to-many relationship for database.
- Using an agile workflow, Django for web development, docker for storage and AWS for hosting

EXPERIENCE DETAILS

UCCS IT, Colorado Springs, CO, IT Technician: Mar 2022 – Nov 2023

- Provided Tier 1 technical support as dedicated Help Desk professional providing technical support in a 15,000+ student and 1,000+ faculty user environment.
- Problem-solver that can communicate with users at all levels of technical proficiency.
- Troubleshoot, resolve, and document user help requests for desktop, laptop, mobile, network and peripheral problems. Platforms include Windows, Mac OS X, iOS, Chrome OS, Android.
- Imaging, configuring, and managing MacOS and Windows machines.
- Troubleshooting: networking, secure VPN, operating systems (iOS, Windows), and printers.
- Maintaining and monitoring 1,000+ machines across campus area network.
- Responsible for teaching/assisting new employees in their daily routines, evaluated performances, critiqued knowledge and performance, and conducted individual assistance.
- Remote administration responsibilities for software and hardware installation across the Campus Area Network, in direct support of students/faculty/staff, and devices.
- Field and implemented intranet and enterprise security policies for the UCCS network infrastructure.

Scheels All Sport, Colorado Springs – Service Shop Technician: Jan 2021 – Feb 2022

• Provided assistance and instructions to customers and fellow associates in maintenance of various products, while providing world class customer service.

Colorado Canine Orthopedics and Rehab – Vet Tech, Technician: Jun 2019 – Mar 2020

• Responsible for performing routine checkups and other medical procedures on animals to ensure their health and well-being.